Guide to the New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Correspondence, 1804-1979
  - Subseries VII.1: Administration
    - Wilson, George, 1889-1896
      - Committees
        - Sound Financial Legislation, Special Committee on, 1895 (Box 296, Folder 8)
        - Sound Financial Legislation, Sub-Committee of the Special Committee on, 1895-1896 (2 Folders) (Box 297, Folder 10-11)
      - Gold Standard, 1896 (Box 296, Folder 9)
  - Subseries VII.2: Gwynne, Charles T., 1916-1941
    Perhaps one of the Chamber’s most dedicated staff members, Charles Gwynne was first employed by the organization as a clerk in 1894. Advancing through the ranks, Gwynne was elected Assistant Secretary, 1909-1915; Secretary, 1915-1924; Vice-President 1922-1924; and Executive Vice-President, 1924-1944. Subseries 2 contains Charles Gwynne’s correspondence with national and international businesses and chambers of commerce, and the Chamber's committees and members; it mostly derives from Gwynne's time as Secretary. Like the materials found in Subseries 1, the items found here are a part of the administration's correspondence; however, because Gwynne retained such a large volume of his correspondence, his materials were given a separate subseries. Due to Gwynne's prolific correspondence it appears that documents were occasionally misfiled; therefore, it may be useful to view folders on similar subjects.
    - General
      - 1919-1920 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - 1920 (Box 198, Folder 1)
      - 1920-1922 (2 Folders) (Box 150, Folder 2-3)
      - 1920-1923 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - 1920-1924 (2 Folders) (Box 150, Folder 5-6)
      - 1920-1924 (Box 289, Folder 1)
      - 1921 (Box 150, Folder 7)
      - 1921-1922 (Box 150, Folder 8)
      - 1921-1924 (3 Folders) (Box 150, Folder 9-11)
      - 1921-1929 (2 Folders) (Box 151, Folder 1-2)
      - 1922 (3 Folders) (Box 151, Folder 3-5)
      - 1922-1923 (5 Folders) (Box 151, Folder 6-10)
      - 1922-1923 (12 Folders) (Box 156, Folder 1-12)
      - 1922-1924 (2 Folders) (Box 152, Folder 1-2)
      - 1922-1929 (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - 1923-1924 (7 Folders) (Box 152, Folder 4-10)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 198, Folder 2)
      - 1923-1924 (6 Folders) (Box 161, Folder 1-6)
      - 1923-1925 (2 Folders) (Box 161, Folder 7-8)
      - 1923-1925 (3 Folders) (Box 153, Folder 1-3)
      - 1924 (2 Folders) (Box 153, Folder 4-5)
      - 1924-1925 (5 Folders) (Box 153, Folder 6-10)
      - 1924-1925 (12 Folders) (Box 154, Folder 1-12)
      - 1924-1925 (2 Folders) (Box 155, Folder 1-2)
      - 1925 (3 Folders) (Box 155, Folder 3-5)
      - 1925-1926 (2 Folders) (Box 155, Folder 6-7)
      - 1925-1926 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - 1926 (4 Folders) (Box 164, Folder 2-5)
    - 155th Annual Banquet, 1923 (2 Folders) (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
    - Acknowledgement of Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee to the School of Business of Columbia University
      - 1924 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - 1924 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - American Chamber of Commerce in London/Greece, 1921-1922 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - American Legion, 1920 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - American Peace Award, 1923-1924 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Aneha, J., 1925 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Arbitration
      - 1921 (Box 289, Folder 4)
      - 1921-1923 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Arbitration Legislature, 1919-1921 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Barge Canal, 1921, (2 Folders) (Box 117, Folder 8-9)
    - Bernheimer, Charles
      - 1922-1923 (Box 198, Folder 4)
      - 1923 (Box 198, Folder 5)
      - Quit Claim Deed, 1918 (Box 289, Folder 6)
      - Portrait, 1925 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Bethell, Union N., Chairman of the Committee on Public Welfare, 1920-1921 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Blackwood, W.A., 1920 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Bowen, Millard, 1921 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce, 1921-1924 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Building Fund Certificates, 1916-1919 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Building Repairs and Improvements, 1907-1923 (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - Bush, Irving T.
      - 1921-1922 (Box 289, Folder 12)
      - 1922 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 117, Folder 13)
      - 1922-1923 (2 Folders) (Box 147, Folder 1-2)
      - 1923-1924 (3 Folders) (Box 147, Folder 3-5)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 289, Folder 13)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 289, Folder 14)
      - Articles, 1923 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Committee on Harbor and Shipping, 1919-1920 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Building Alterations and Repairs
      - 1921 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - 1921-1922 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Business Information Requests from other Cities, 1922-1924 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Calendar Reform, 1922-1923 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Cathedral of St. John the Divine, 1924-1925 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Certificate of Ownership from the Broadway Tabernacle Society, 1912-1920 (Box 289, Folder 15)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the Borough of Queens
      - 1922-1923 (Box 159, Folder 2)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Julius Henry, Counsel, 1919-1922 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Committee Appointments, 1924 (Box 289, Folder 16)
    - Committee Nominations, 1925 (Box 289, Folder 17)
    - Committees
      - One Hundred, Committee of, 1919 (Box 289, Folder 18)
      - Arbitration, Committee on
        - 1919-1921 (Box 289, Folder 19)
        - 1920-1922 (Box 198, Folder 8)
        - 1921 (Box 290, Folder 1)
        - 1921-1922 (Box 290, Folder 2)
      - Commercial Education, Committee on
        - 1920-1922 (Box 290, Folder 3)
        - 1921-1924 (Box 290, Folder 4)
        - 1923 (Box 198, Folder 9)
      - Conservation of State Waters, Lands and Forests, 1919-1921 (Box 290, Folder 5)
      - Cooperate with the Lower Taxes-Less Legislation League, Committee to, 1924 (Box 290, Folder 6)
      - Defense, Special Committee on, 1917-1920 (Box 195, Folder 1)
      - Diversion of Freight for Export from the Port of New York, Sub-Committee on, 1920 (Box 195, Folder 2)
      - Finance and Currency, Committee on
        - 1919-1920 (Box 198, Folder 10)
        - 1919-1920 (Box 290, Folder 7)
        - 1920-1922 (Box 290, Folder 8)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 198, Folder 11)
        - 1922-1924 (Box 290, Folder 9)
      - Foreign Commerce and Revenue Laws, Committee on
        - 1919 (Box 198, Folder 12)
        - 1919-1920 (2 Folders) (Box 198, Folder 13-14)
        - 1919-1920 (Box 290, Folder 10)
        - 1920-1921 (Box 290, Folder 11)
        - 1921 (Box 291, Folder 1)
        - 1921-1923 (Box 198, Folder 15)
        - 1922 (Box 159, Folder 6)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 291, Folder 2)
      - Harbor and Shipping, Committee on
        - 1918-1920 (Box 198, Folder 16)
        - 1919-1921 (Box 291, Folder 3)
        - 1920-1921 (2 Folders) (Box 291, Folder 4-5)
        - 1920-1923 (Box 195, Folder 3)
        - 1921-1922 (Box 159, Folder 7)
        - 1922 (Box 159, Folder 8)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 195, Folder 4)
        - 1923 (Box 195, Folder 5)
        - 1923-1924 (2 Folders) (Box 291, Folder 6-7)
      - Hearing on the return of funds held by Alien Property Custodian, 1925 (Box 159, Folder 9)
      - Industrial Problems and Relations, Committee on, 1919-1921 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Industrial Problems and Relations, Special Committee on, 1921-1922 (Box 291, Folder 8)
      - Insurance, Committee on
        - 1919-1920 (Box 195, Folder 6)
        - 1920 (Box 195, Folder 7)
        - 1920-1921 (Box 118, Folder 2)
        - 1921 (Box 291, Folder 9)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 195, Folder 8)
      - Internal Trade and Improvements, Committee on
        - 1919-1920 (Box 195, Folder 9)
        - 1919-1920 (Box 179, Folder 1)
        - 1919-1921 (Box 118, Folder 3)
        - 1920-1921 (Box 292, Folder 1)
        - 1921-1922 (Box 292, Folder 2)
        - 1922-1923 (3 Folders) (Box 118, Folder 4-6)
        - 1923 (Box 118, Folder 7)
        - 1923 (Box 179, Folder 2)
        - 1923-1924 (Box 292, Folder 3)
        - Railroad Consolidation, 1923 (Box 292, Folder 4)
      - National Budget, Committee on a, 1920-1921 (Box 159, Folder 10)
      - National Budget, Committee on a--Freeman, Charles D., 1920 (Box 159, Folder 11)
      - Organization of Commercial Bodies, Committee on the, 1923 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Publications, Special Committee on--Annual Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - Public Service in the Metropolitan District, Committee on
        - 1920-1922 (Box 118, Folder 9)
        - 1921 (Box 118, Folder 10)
        - 1922 (Box 118, Folder 11)
        - 1922 (Box 179, Folder 3)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 179, Folder 4)
        - 1923-1924 (2 Folders) (Box 292, Folder 5)
        - Traffic Conditions, 1924 (Box 292, Folder 6)
      - Public Welfare, Committee on
        - 1920 (Box 179, Folder 5)
        - Sub-Committee on Defense, 1920-1921 (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Public Welfare, Special Committee on, 1920 (Box 158, Folder 2)
      - Registration, Sub-Committee of the Executive Committee on, 1922 (Box 195, Folder 10)
      - Relief, Committee on--Mrs. Marcus H. Tracy, 1935-1941 (Box 179, Folder 7)
      - Representing the NYCC on the Joint Committee, Committee,1922 (Box 195, Folder 11)
      - Revision of By-Laws, Special Committee on, 1924 (Box 195, Folder 12)
      - Senator La Follete’s Proposed Legislation, Sub-Committee of the Executive Committee on, 1923 (Box 195, Folder 13)
      - Taxation, Committee on
        - 1919-1922 (Box 292, Folder 7)
        - 1922 (Box 179, Folder 8)
        - 1922-1924 (2 Folders) (Box 293, Folder 1-2)
      - Thrift, Committee on, 1919-1921 (Box 179, Folder 9)
      - Trade Relations, Joint Committee on, 1923 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Conference regarding Diversion of Export Freight from New York to Other Ports, 1920 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Conventions, 1923-1924 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Data for Annual Report, 1918 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Dime for Outclassing Rockefeller, 1929 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Dingle, Edwin J., 1921-1922 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Discrimination of North Atlantic Ports and Railroads, 1920 (2 Folders) (Box 162, Folder 1-2)
    - Eastern Apple Exposition and Fruit Fair Essay Contest, 1923 (2 Folders) (Box 162, Folder 3-4)
    - Ecker, Frederick
      - 1923-1924 (Box 162, Folder 5)
      - 1924 (2 Folders) (Box 293, Folder 6-7)
      - 1925 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - Eisman, Max, 1923-1924 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - European Tour
      - 1924 (3 Folders) (Box 162, Folder 7-9)
      - 1927 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee
      - 1919-1921 (Box 293, Folder 9)
      - 1920-1922 (Box 294, Folder 1)
      - 1920-1924 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Federal Seaman Compensation Bill, 1921 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Fontaine/Textiles, 1923 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Foreign Trade, 1916-1924 (3 Folders) (Box 294, Folder 2-4)
    - Form Letters, 1919-1922 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Haller, Josef Visit, 1923 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Harbors and Shipping
      - 1919 (Box 294, Folder 6)
      - 1920 (Box 162, Folder 14)
      - Harlem River, 1921 (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Hearing on Port Authority Plans, 1922 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Hostility Toward New York, 1922 (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - House Committee, 1921-1922 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Hudson Valley Federated Chamber of Commerce, 1925-1926 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Hughes, Charles E., 1925 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Hydrographic Office, 1920-1921 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - The Intercollegiate Cosmopolitan Club Reception, 1923 (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - International Joint Commission on the St. Lawrence Ship Canal, 1920 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Kingsley, Darwin P.
    - 1921 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - 1921-1922 (2 Folders) (Box 148, Folder 2-3)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Insurance, 1919-1920 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Kyoto Round-the-World Party, 1925-1927 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Luncheon
      - Bush, Irving T., 1923 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Chinese High Commission, 1924 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Meeting, 1923 (Box 294, Folder 9)
      - Newly Elected Members (Box 148, Folder 9)
        - 1923 February (Box 148, Folder 10)
        - 1923 March (Box 148, Folder 11)
        - 1923 April (Box 148, Folder 12)
        - 1923 May (Box 148, Folder 13)
        - 1923 December (Box 148, Folder 14)
        - 1924 May (Box 294, Folder 10)
      - Relation to the National Retail Dry Goods Association Convention, 1923 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Lusk Report, 1923 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Maps, Undated (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Marling, Alfred E., 1921-1923 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Marshall Stillman Movement, 1923-1924 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Mellon Tax Reduction Plan, 1923 (Box 294, Folder 13)
    - Membership, 1925 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Membership Luncheon, 1923-1924 (2 Folders) (Box 199, Folder 4-5)
    - The Merchants Association of New York, 1921-1924 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Monthly Meetings, 1924-1925 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce Funds, 1912-1934 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - New York State Waterways Conference Committee--Recording Secretary
      - 1921-1923 (3 Folders) (Box 199, Folder 7-9)
      - 1923-1925 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Narrative of European Tour, 1924 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - National Civic Federation, 1919-1924 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - National Defense, 1922-1923 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce Commercial Examination Awards, 1923-1924 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Nominating Committee, 1922-1923 (2 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 5-6)
    - Outerbridge, E.H., 1919-1923 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Peace Treaty, 1919-1920 (2 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 7-8)
    - Peed, Garland Powell, New Membership Campaign, 1941-1942 (2 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 9-10)
    - Personal, 1917-1919 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Plan for the Comprehensive Development of the Port of New York, 1921-1923 (2 Folders) (Box 157, Folder 1-2)
    - Pollution of Navigable Waters; Pontoon Bridge, Hudson River, 1921 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Port and Harbor Development, 1920-1921 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Port Treaty, 1920 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Public Service Commission, 1922 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Public Welfare, 1922-1923 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Purchase of Cape Cod Canal, 1923 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Reception for Lloyd George, 1923 (4 Folders) (Box 196, Folder 2-5)
    - Reconstruction Commission/Consumption Tax, 1919-1920 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Report on Arbitration Court of the Chamber of Commerce, 1922-1923 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Representatives of the Commercial Organizations of New York State, 1920-1922 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Requests and Inquiries
      - 1920-1924 (Box 295, Folder 7)
      - 1921-1924 (Box 295, Folder 8)
      - 1922-1923 (2 Folders) (Box 295, Folder 9-10)
      - 1923-1924 (2 Folders) (Box 196, Folder 9-10)
      - 1923-1924 (5 Folders) (Box 197, Folder 1-5)
    - Revision of the New York City Charter, 1922 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Ring, Welding, 1919-1921 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Russia
      - 1919-1920 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - 1919-1920 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Safeguarding Small Investors, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Safeguarding Small Investors, 1922-1923 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Schwab, Gustav, 1915 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Philip D., 1923 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Southern Exposition, 1924-1925 (2 Folders) (Box 296, Folder 1-2)
    - Staten Island Ferry Service, 1920-1921 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - St. Lawrence Canal
      - 1920-1921 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - 1920-1922 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Sterling Bill, 1923 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Thrift Citizens Movement, 1919-1921 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Transportation Congestion Meeting, 1920 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce, 1921-1925 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Use of the Great Hall, 1923 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Viviani, René, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Yale University Press Film Service, 1925 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Subseries VII.3: Subject Files, 1804-1979
    The correspondence subject files in subseries 3 remains true to its original order, though researchers should note that the original arrangement appears to have been contrived by the organization itself in the second half of the 20th century. The correspondence found here focuses on a wide range of topics, and derives largely from the 19th century. Subjects of local concern, such as urban development, New York City harbor defense, and sanitation are noted. National issues related to commerce and industry also figure into the correspondence in this subseries; the Chamber's involvement with the establishment of the first transatlantic cable, international canals as a means of transport, national currency, interstate commerce, and government offices are all subjects addressed here. Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - General
      - Undated (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - 1816-1907 (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - 1830-1839 (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - 1840-1849 (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - 1841-1937, (2 Folders) (Box 225, Folder 5-6)
      - 1850-1859 (Box 225, Folder 7)
      - 1860-1869 (3 Folders) (Box 225, Folder 8-10)
      - 1870-1879 (Box 225, Folder 11)
      - 1870-1879, (2 Folders) (Box 226, Folder 1-2)
      - 1880-1885 (Box 226, Folder 3)
      - 1880-1889 (Box 226, Folder 4)
      - 1880-1908 (Box 226, Folder 5)
      - 1890-1899 (Box 226, Folder 6)
      - 1900-1909 (Box 226, Folder 7)
      - 1910-1919 (Box 226, Folder 8)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 226, Folder 9)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 226, Folder 10)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 226, Folder 11)
      - 1970-1979 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Academy of Medicine, 1896 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Acknowledgements, 1877-1934 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Annual Banquets, 1887-1900 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Arbitration, 1804-1866 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Arbitration, 1822-1911 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - Arbitration, 1851-1886 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - Assay Office, 1853-1863 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Association of Partners of Stock Exchange Firms, 1913 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - Assessments, 1862 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - Atlantic Cable, 1862-1864 (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - Atlantic Cable--Dinner for Cyrus Field, 1866 (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - Atlantic Cable Portrait, 1893-1895 (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - Aviation, 1862 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Bankruptcy, 1840-1889 (Box 227, Folder 14)
    - Banking Laws--New York City, 1838-1864 (Box 227, Folder 15)
    - Bark Maury, 1855-1863 (Box 227, Folder 16)
    - Battery Extension, 1857-1870 (Box 227, Folder 17)
    - Benner, Hiram H., Case, 1879-1906 (Box 227, Folder 18)
    - Bills of Lading, 1875-1885 (Box 227, Folder 19)
    - Board of Commissioners of Pilots, 1896-1931 (Box 227, Folder 20)
    - Bookkeeping, 1848-1849 (Box 227, Folder 21)
    - Brazil, 1863-1865 (Box 227, Folder 22)
    - Bureau of American Republics, 1898 (Box 227, Folder 23)
    - California, 1864-1866 (Box 227, Folder 24)
    - Canals
      - Inter Oceanic Nicaragua, 1879-1901 (Box 227, Folder 25)
      - New York State, 1857-1882 (Box 228, Folder 1)
      - Panama, 1909-1912 (Box 228, Folder 2)
      - Suez, 1865-1871 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Census, 1828-1891 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Central System, 1866-1878 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Certification of Origin, 1911 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1912-1913 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Chambers of Commerce, 1838-1902 (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Charleston, 1896 (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - "Charter, By-Laws, and Organization of the Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York", 1844 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Cheap Transportation Association, 1867-1877 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Fire, 1871-1872 (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - China, 1844-1918 (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Cholera Outbreaks--Swine Disease, 1883 (Box 228, Folder 14)
    - Citizens Budget Commission, 1932 (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - City Development and Planning, 1912 (Box 228, Folder 16)
    - City Hall--Geography, 1867 (Box 228, Folder 17)
    - Civil War--United States, 1862-1868 (Box 228, Folder 18)
    - Clinton Vases, 1893-1908 (Box 228, Folder 19)
    - Coast Survey, 1845-1862 (Box 228, Folder 20)
    - Collector of the Port, 1849 (Box 228, Folder 21)
    - Colleges of Commerce in New York City, 1899-1915 (Box 228, Folder 22)
    - Committees
      - Claims Against the Government, Committee on, 1850-1857 (Box 229, Folder 1)
      - Seigniorage, Committee on, 1853 (Box 229, Folder 2)
      - Sherman Statue, Committee on the, 1891-1913 (Box 229, Folder 3)
      - Wharves, Piers and Slips, Committee on, 1836-1910 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Communications with New York State Government Officials
      - 1837-1914 (2 Folders) (Box 229, Folder 5-6)
      - 1849-1892 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Consular Service, 1862-1894 (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Copyright
      - Monthly Bulletin, 1939-1963 (Box 229, Folder 9)
      - Monthly Bulletin, 1960-1964 (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Cotton, 1843-1898 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Cuba, 1853-1902 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Currency
      - 1837-1873 (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Silver, 1891-1894 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Custom House
      - Administration, 1862 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Forms, 1858-1879 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Customs Inspection, 1836-1856 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Danish Sound Dues, 1853 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Debtors--Nonresident, 1839 (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Debts of the Southern States, 1861 (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Department of Commerce and Labor, 1907 (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Defense, 1860-1893 (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - Diving Apparatus, 1857 (Box 230, Folder 13)
    - Dodge Statue, 1883-1885 (Box 230, Folder 14)
    - Dudley Observatory, 1856 (Box 230, Folder 15)
    - Duties Collection, 1856-1867 (Box 230, Folder 16)
    - Ecuador, 1880 (Box 230, Folder 17)
    - England, 1862 (Box 230, Folder 18)
    - Expeditions, 1863 1893 (Box 230, Folder 19)
    - Fire Department--New York City, 1856 (Box 230, Folder 20)
    - Flynn’s Knoll Lighthouse, 1842 (Box 374, Folder 14)
    - France, 1850-1893 (Box 230, Folder 21)
    - Francis, Joseph, 1889-1892 (Box 230, Folder 22)
    - Freight, 1885-1913 (Box 230, Folder 23)
    - Garfield, President James A., 1881 (Box 230, Folder 24)
    - General Average, 1860-1878 (Box 230, Folder 25)
    - Germany, 1883 (Box 230, Folder 26)
    - Gifts, 1833-1859 (Box 230, Folder 27)
    - Governor’s Island, 1912 (Box 230, Folder 28)
    - Grant’s Tomb, 1928-1930 (Box 230, Folder 29)
    - Harbor Defense--New York City, 1863 (Box 230, Folder 30)
    - Harbor Master’s Bill, 1862 (Box 230, Folder 31)
    - Harbor Supervisor, 1884 (Box 230, Folder 32)
    - History of Commerce--United States, 1863-1910 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Honorary Members, 1860-1910 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Hudson River Navigation, 1845 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Immigration, 1862-1867 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Institution for the Savings of Merchants’ Clerk, 1847-1909 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1844-1914 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - International Law, 1877 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - International Reciprocity, 1853-1865 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Interstate Commerce, 1879 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Italy, 1909 (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Japan, 1860-1872 (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - Korea, 1883 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Labor, 1868-1913 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - Langeloth Home, 1914 (Box 231, Folder 14)
    - Laws Related to Principals and Factors or Agents, 1825 (Box 231, Folder 15)
    - Letters of Appreciation, 1837-1866 (Box 231, Folder 16)
    - Lexon Committee, 1894-1895 (Box 231, Folder 17)
    - Life Preservation--Marine, 1840-1870 (Box 231, Folder 18)
    - Life Preservers--Steam Boats, 1821 (Box 231, Folder 19)
    - Lighthouses, 1838-1867 (Box 231, Folder 20)
    - Lincoln, Abraham--Death, 1865 (Box 231, Folder 21)